Peter Fallon - Gallery Press collection, circa 1967-1998
Emory University
- Literary manuscripts, 1969-1998, Series 1; Boxes 1-111
  - Gallery Press author files, 1969-1998, Subseries 1.1; Boxes 1-85
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, The Astrakhan Cloak, Proofs with corrections (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, The Astrakhan Cloak, Proofs with corrections (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, The Astrakhan Cloak, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, The Astrakhan Cloak, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, Pharaoh's Daughter, Miscellaneous (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, Pharaoh's Daughter, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, Pharaoh's Daughter, Proofs with corrections (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, Pharaoh's Daughter, Proofs with corrections (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, Pharaoh's Daughter, Proofs with corrections (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, Pharaoh's Daughter, Proofs with corrections (English) (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, Pharaoh's Daughter, Proofs with corrections (incomplete) (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, Pharaoh's Daughter, TS poems with corrections (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, Pharaoh's Daughter, TS poems with corrections (English) (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, Pharaoh's Daughter, TS poems with corrections (Irish) (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Nolan, Jim, Biographical (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Nolan, Jim, Book jacket material (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Nolan, Jim, Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Nolan, Jim, Playbills (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Nolan, Jim, "The Black Pool," TS (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Nolan, Jim, "The Boathouse," TS (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Nolan, Jim, "Guernica Hotel," TS (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Nolan, Jim, "Guernica Hotel," TS (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Nolan, Jim, Moonshine, TS (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Nolan, Jim, Moonshine, TS (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Nolan, Jim, Moonshine, TS with corrections (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Nolan, Jim, Moonshine, Proofs with corrections (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Nolan, Jim, Moonshine, Proofs with corrections (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - O'Callaghan, Conor, Biographical (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - O'Callaghan, Conor, Book jacket material (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - O'Callaghan, Conor, Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - O'Callaghan, Conor, Correspondence, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - O'Callaghan, Conor, Miscellaneous (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - O'Callaghan, Conor, The History of Rain, TS with corrections (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - O'Callaghan, Conor, The History of Rain, TS with corrections (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - O'Callaghan, Conor, The History of Rain, Proofs with corrections (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - O'Callaghan, Conor, The History of Rain, Proofs with corrections (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - O'Callaghan, Conor, The History of Rain, Proofs with corrections (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - O'Callaghan, Conor, "The Planter's Son" (photocopy) (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - O'Donoghue, Bernard, Biographical (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - O'Donoghue, Bernard, Correspondence, 1986-1991 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - O'Donoghue, Bernard, Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - O'Donoghue, Bernard, Correspondence, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - O'Donoghue, Bernard, Other published works (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - O'Donoghue, Bernard, Poaching Rights, Corrected proofs (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - O'Donoghue, Bernard, Poaching Rights, Uncorrected proofs (Box OP85)
    - O'Donoghue, Bernard, Poaching Rights, TS poems (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - O'Donoghue, Gregory, Biographical (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - O'Donoghue, Gregory, Correspondence, 1975-1996 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - O'Donoghue, Gregory, Miscellaneous (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - O'Donoghue, Gregory, Other published works (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - O'Donoghue, Gregory, "Degree Absolute," TS poem (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - O'Donoghue, Gregory, Kicking, TS with corrections (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - O'Donoghue, Gregory, Kicking, Proofs with corrections (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - O'Donoghue, Gregory, Kicking, Proofs with corrections (Box OP47)
    - O'Donoghue, Gregory, Open Map, TS with corrections (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - O'Faoláin, Seán [See: Hayes, Maurice (ed.), Flight Path] (Box -, Folder -)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Biographical (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Book jacket material (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Correspondence, 1977-1982 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Correspondence, 1984-1994 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Correspondence, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Miscellaneous (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Other published works (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Portraits (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Proofs with corrections (Box OP48)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Writings by Others (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Alexandrian Attitudes, TS with corrections (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, "Belfast," MS (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, "Giséle Triptych," TS (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, The Greek Anthology, TS (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Headgear of the Tribe, TS (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Headgear of the Tribe, Proof with author's corrections (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Headgear of the Tribe, Proof with corrections (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Irish Anthology, TS (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, A Limerick Rake, TS with corrections (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, "The Limerick Rake," MS poem (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, "Loner," MS (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Ogoms, TS (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, "Raftery the Poet," MS (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Seven Arab Odes, TS (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, "Sidelines," TS (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Sing Me Creation, MS and TS (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, His Skaldcrow's Nest, TS (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, "These Fields in Springtime," TS (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Trawling the Tradition, TS with corrections (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Trawling the Tradition, TS with corrections (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, The Unathourised Version, TS with corrections (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, Untitled, MS (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, "The Wandering Celt," MS (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, The Wandering Celt, TS with corrections (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, The Wandering Celt, TS (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Ó Muirthile, Liam, Biographical (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Ó Muirthile, Liam, Book jacket material (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Ó Muirthile, Liam, Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Ó Muirthile, Liam, Miscellaneous (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Ó Muirthile, Liam, Other published works (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Ó Muirthile, Liam, "An Chulturlann," TS (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Ó Muirthile, Liam, "Carraig Aifrinn," TS (Box 76, Folder 23)
    - O'Murithile, Liam, Dialann Bóthair, Proofs with corrections (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Ó Muirthile, Liam, Dialann Bóthair, Proofs with corrections (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Ó Muirthile, Liam, Dialann Bóthair, TS with corrections (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Ó Muirthile, Liam, "Faoi Uisce," TS with corrections (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Ó Muirthile, Liam, "Feartlaoi Francois Villon," TS (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Ó Muirthile, Liam, "Náisiún na mSailte Fearann," MS (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Ó Muirthile, Liam, "Riuce Gréagach," TS (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Ormsby, Frank, Biographical (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Ormsby, Frank, Book jacket material (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Ormsby, Frank, Correspondence, 1970-1988 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Ormsby, Frank, Correspondence, 1989-1995 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Ormsby, Frank, Miscellaneous (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Ormsby, Frank, Newspaper Clipping (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Ormsby, Frank, "A Belfast Journal," TS (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Ormsby, Frank, "A Belfast Journal," TS (Box OP49)
    - Ormsby, Frank, "The Disappearance of the Lough," TS (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Ormsby, Frank, "Getting Married," TS (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Ormsby, Frank, The Ghost Train, TS with corrections (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Ormsby, Frank, The Ghost Train, Proofs with corrections (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Ormsby, Frank, "Losing a Day," TS (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - Ormsby, Frank, "The Mechanics," TS (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - Ormsby, Frank, "The Mechanics," TS (Box OP50)
    - Ormsby, Frank, A Northern Spring, Corrected Proofs (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Ormsby, Frank, A Northern Spring, TS (Box OP51)
    - Ormsby, Frank, "The Security Man," TS (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Ormsby, Frank, "The Security Man," TS (Box OP52)
    - Ormsby, Frank, "The Sleepwalker," TS (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Ormsby, Frank, "A Small Town in Ireland," TS (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Ormsby, Frank, A Store of Candles, Corrected proofs (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Ormsby, Frank, "Waiting for a Connection," TS (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Ó Tuama, Seán, Biographical (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Ó Tuama, Seán, Correspondence, 1986-1991 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Ó Tuama, Seán, Miscellaneous (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Ó Tuama, Seán, Other published works (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Ó Tuama, Seán, AN BÁSI dTÍR NA nÓG [Coiscéim, 1988], TS with corrections (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Ó Tuama, Seán, "Besides Who Knows...," TS (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Ó Tuama, Seán, "Greek Waters," TS (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Ó Tuama, Seán, "A Musician's Loveletter," TS (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Parker, Stewart, Biographical (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Parker, Stewart, Book jacket material (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Parker, Stewart, Correspondence, 1979-1987 (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Parker, Stewart, Miscellaneous (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Parker, Stewart, Playbill (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - Parker, Stewart, Catchpenny Twist, Proofs with corrections (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - Parker, Stewart, Catchpenny Twist, TS (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - Parker, Stewart, Heavenly Bodies, TS (Box 78, Folder 22)
    - Parker, Stewart, I'm a Dreamer Montreal, TS (Box 78, Folder 23)
    - Parker, Stewart, "The Kamikaze Ground Staff Reunion Dinner," TS (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Parker, Stewart, Northern Star, TS (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Parker, Stewart, Pentecost, TS (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Reardon, Daniel, Biographical (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Reardon, Daniel, Book jacket material (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Reardon, Daniel, Correspondence, 1984-1993 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Reardon, Daniel, TS poems (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Reardon, Daniel, In the Lion House, Proof with corrections (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Reardon, Daniel, In the Lion House, TS with corrections (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Reardon, Daniel, "The Seagull Affair," MS (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Reardon, Daniel, Spenser's Laye, TS (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Reardon, Daniel, "Stillorgay Road," MS (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Reardon, Daniel, Untitled MS (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Rodgers, W.R., Biographical (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Rodgers, W.R., Correspondence, 1991-1996 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Rodgers, W.R., Drawing (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Rodgers, W.R., Miscellaneous (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Rodgers, W.R., Poems, Proof with corrections (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Rodgers, W.R., Poems, Proof with corrections (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Rodgers, W.R., "Spring-Dance," TS (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Simmons, James, Artwork (sketch by Simmons for Peter Fallon) (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Simmons, James, Biographical (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Simmons, James, Book jacket material (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Simmons, James, Correspondence, 1970-1985 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Simmons, James, Correspondence, 1986-1994 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Simmons, James, Correspondence, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Simmons, James, Miscellaneous (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Simmons, James, Other published works (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Simmons, James, TS poems (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Simmons, James, "Dolly McCartney's Africa" (theatre review), TS with corrections (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Simmons, James, From the Irish [Blackstaff, 1985], TS with corrections (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Simmons, James, Poems 1956-1986, Cover Art by Michael Kane (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Simmons, James, Poems 1956-1986, Proofs with corrections (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Simmons, James, Poems 1956-1986, Proofs with corrections (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Simmons, James, Poems 1956-1986, Proofs with corrections (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Simmons, James, Poems 1956-1986, Proofs with corrections (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Simmons, James, Poems 1956-1986, Proofs with corrections (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Simmons, James, Poems 1956-1986, Proofs with corrections (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Simmons, James, Poems 1956-1986, Proofs with corrections (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Simmons, James, "Sexual Encounters," TS of table of contents (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Simmons, James, "War on Want," TS with corrections (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Sirr, Peter, Biographical (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Sirr, Peter, Book jacket material (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Sirr, Peter, Correspondence, 1983-1995 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Sirr, Peter, Correspondence, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Sirr, Peter, Miscellaneous (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Sirr, Peter, Other published works (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Sirr, Peter, The Ledger of Fruitful Exchange, TS with corrections (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Sirr, Peter, The Ledger of Fruitful Exchange, TS with corrections (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Sirr, Peter, The Ledger of Fruitful Exchange, TS with corrections (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Sirr, Peter, The Ledger of Fruitful Exchange, Proofs with corrections (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Sirr, Peter, "Journeying Inland," [variant title of Marginal Zones] TS with corrections (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Sirr, Peter, Marginal Zones, Original cover art by Michael Kane (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Sirr, Peter - Marginal Zones, Proofs with corrections (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Sirr, Peter, Marginal Zones, TS with corrections (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Sirr, Peter, "Nights Now with You," [variant title of Talk, Talk] MS and TS with corrections (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Sirr, Peter, Talk, Talk, Proof with corrections (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Sirr, Peter, Talk, Talk, TS with corrections (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Sirr, Peter, Ways of Falling, Cover art (Box OP86)
    - Sirr, Peter, Ways of Falling, MS and TS with corrections (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Sirr, Peter, Ways of Falling, Proof with corrections (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Sirr, Peter, Ways of Falling, TS with corrections (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Paul [See Hayes, Maurice (ed.) - Flight Path] (Box -, Folder -)
    - Wheatley, David, Biographical (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Wheatley, David, Book jacket material (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Wheatley, David, Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Wheatley, David, Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Wheatley, David, Correspondence, n.d. (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Wheatley, David, Correspondence, n.d. (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Wheatley, David, Miscellaneous (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Wheatley, David, Other published works (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Wheatley, David, TS poems [contains some poems from Misery Hill and correspondence to Peter Fallon] (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Wheatley, David, Unpublished prose, TS (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Wheatley, David, Thirst, Computer disk (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Wheatley, David, Thirst, Proof with corrections (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Wheatley, David, Thirst, Proof with corrections (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Wheatley, David, Thirst, TS with corrections (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Wheatley, David, Thirst, TS with corrections (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Gallery Press submission files, ca. 1966-1997, Subseries 1.2; Boxes 87-99
    Organized into three parts: Correspondence, Poetry submissions, and Prose submissions.
    - Correspondence
    - 1966-1971 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - 1972-1974 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - 1979-1981 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - 1982-1984 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - 1985 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - 1986 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - 1987 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - 1988 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - 1989 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - 1990 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - January-May 1991 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - June-December, n.d. 1991 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - January-July 1992 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - August-December, n.d. 1992 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - January-June 1993 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - July-December 1993 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - 1994 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - January-June 1995 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - July-December 1995 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - January-June 1996 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - July-December 1996 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - January-June 1997 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - July-December 1997 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - n.d. 1990's (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - n.d. 1990's (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - n.d. (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - n.d. (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Poetry Submissions
    - Allen-Devine, B. (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Anderson, Nathalie F. (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Anne, Pasrau Mee (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Barry, Sebastian (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Beau-Bradley, Zephyr (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Beirne, Gerry (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Brett, Heather (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Broic, Adharca (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Brook, Donna (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Brown, Anne (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Byre, Abbie (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Byrne, Vincent (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Cantu, Gil (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Casey, Philip (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Colacino, Anthony (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Conolly, Declan (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Contogenis, Constantine (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Cooper, Emily (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Cox, Gary Noel (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Crither, Dorneal (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Darragh, Simon (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Deane, John F. (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - De Bhal, Liam [William Wall] (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - De Paor, Frank (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Delanty, Greg (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Dempsey, Patrick (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Donnelly, Charles (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Downey, William Gerald (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Drew, John (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Dunne, James (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Elliot, Andrew (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Emmott, Stewart Earl (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Fanning, Gerard (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Flatley, Pete (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Friesen, Lauren (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Frodhe, Anders (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - Garcia Alonso, Augustin (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - George, Barry (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - Golden, Frank (Box 92, Folder 21)
    - Gordon, Dónal Kevin (Box 92, Folder 22)
    - Granier, Mark (Box 92, Folder 23)
    - Grant, Richard (Box 92, Folder 24)
    - Guyer, Christopher (Box 92, Folder 25)
    - Halton, Pauline (Box 92, Folder 26)
    - Hanshaw, R.A. (Box 92, Folder 27)
    - Hermann, Gunilla (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Hickey, Verette (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Holland, Jade (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Horrigan, Thomas (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Hubert, Anita (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Johnston, Fred (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Jones, Roland (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Kelly, Mary (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Kennard, Alex. (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Lalor, Brian (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Lamarck, Leonard (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Latham, Alison (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Lintott, Alison J (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Lustig, Ian (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Lynch, Susan (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - McAuley, James (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - McCarthy, Patricia (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - McCarthy, Ted (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - McCarthy, Thomas (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - McCarty, Veve (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - McConnells, Peter (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - McDonald, Peter (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Maher, Adrienne (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Makhija, Anju (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Mann, James (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Maynard, T.B. (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Millen, Cynthia M. (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Miller, David Carson (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Mitjushev, Pavel (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Montano, Linda Ravenswood (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Mooney, Martin (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Moran, Patrick (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Morrissey, Sinéad (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Moses, Antoinette (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Mullen, Ned (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Murphy, Tim (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Muscat, John P. (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Nash, William P. (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Nelson, Geoffrey K. (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Ney, Sandra (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - Ni Ghlinn, Aine (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - Nugent, Colin (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - O'Brien, Mary (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - O'Donovan, Noel (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - O'Neill, Peter (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - O'Shea, Rosemary (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - O'Shea, Suzanne (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - O'Sullivan, Mark (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Orth, Kevin (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Postema, W. (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Power, Edward (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Ray, Joanne (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Rivers, Ann (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Rixulodus (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - RMX (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Rua, Mael Coll (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Ryan, Louis (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - Ryan, Patrick (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Scott, David (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - Shea, Glenn (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - Sheridan, Jim (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - Smith, Michael (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - Smith, Michael (Box OP54)
    - Smith, Miss (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - Smyth, Gerard (Box 95, Folder 23)
    - Smythe, Norman (Box 95, Folder 24)
    - Tessie, Thom (Box 95, Folder 25)
    - Thamm, James (Box 95, Folder 26)
    - Tinley, Bill (Box 95, Folder 27)
    - Wall, Eamonn (Box 95, Folder 28)
    - Welch, Robert (Box OP55)
    - White, Edward (Box 95, Folder 29)
    - Wright, Howard (Box 95, Folder 30)
    - Wrigley, P. (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - n.d. (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - n.d. (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - n.d. (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - n.d. (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Prose Submissions
    - Atkinson, C.J. (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Bradshaw, William (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Brazil, Edward (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Byrne, Louie (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Canter, John D. (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Dillon, Eilís (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Fleming, Thomas (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Furlong, Stella (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Gallagher, Francis J. (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Gentili, Alessandro (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Gilbride, Richard (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Graham, Stephen (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Hackett, Owen (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Hanrahan, John (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Hogan, Des (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Keane, John B. (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Keery, Sam (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - King, Joeseph and Betty (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Leonard, Hugh (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - Leonard, Hugh (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Leonard, Hugh (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Lewis, David (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Lincecum, Jerry (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Mac Mathúna, Seán (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Makin, Leonard (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Manson, A.M. (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Martin, Emer (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Mercier, Paul (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Millen, Cynthia M. (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Mitchell, Gary (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Montobbio, Santiago (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - O'Brien, John C. (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - O'Callaghan, John J. (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Ó Tuairisc, Eoghan (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Radner, Joan (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Robinson, Leslie W. (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - St. John, John (Box 99, Folder 4)